Seino, gulagaru channel! Gogo!
Today I would like to do Talma's Corona Dancer!
I did it last time, or rather, twice, but I'm not in it.
Me neither.
What do you think?
All of you?
Oh, no.
Let me explain the rules a little bit.
Wow, this is hard.
I hope you all understand.
Well, first of all...
As soon as you decide.
I'm scared.
One ogre will be chosen.
The ogre will play music by Girls Girls Girls.
Then, the non-Ogre dances during the time.
Then the ogre stops the dance at his/her own timing.
Then the dancer stops at the same time.
Then, the ogre goes like this...
Watching?
Please stop at the same time.
No matter what they do.
I understand.
That was easy to understand.
Thank you very much.
Well done.
Thank you.
Now let's get on with it.
Video, start!
This time, I am wearing a costume by D-Holic.
Q.What kind of costumes are you going to put on?
A.It is 2 for Ms. Minami.
Please have 2 watch from behind and fasten it anytime.
Okay, I'm going.
I'm scared.
Scary.Scary.
It's never gonna change.
Then I'll make the rounds.
That's how it feels.
Oh, I see! That's great!
Oh, I see! Amazing!
Your smile is fixed, too, To-chan.
Well, let's continue. Ready!
Oh, no! This is so hard!
Good luck!
You always move on, Misaki.
Isn't that great? You're good.
That's great.
Is she going to be okay?
Are you guys okay, Yuzu?
Are you okay?
Leader, are you okay?
Isn't it amazing? Why can't we stop like this?
Let's continue.
I hate this game.
It's so exhausting.
It's exhausting.
I'm tired of this too!
Please don't stop.
Don't stop at the weirdest places.
It's okay, it's okay.
I've already got one foot in the door.
I'm gonna make you wait a long time.
You look like a campaign worker.
Are you okay?
You're out! You're out!
I can't do this anymore.
It's too much?
It's too hard.
You're good.Excellent.
They're all good.
Are you okay with the faces? What's this?
If we could just lock the shoulders.
Glengüe, length.
I can't dance.
You'd laugh and move.
Wait a minute, let me back up to the snipe rustle.
Tight.
Oh, yuck.
That's a good one, too.
Where was I?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Oh, it's hard, it's hard, it's hard, it's hard.
Your hand is totally up.
You're being a little bit mean, aren't you?
You're like a mascot, aren't you?
Tarataran.
Oh, no!
No!
I'm off!
Oh, well, this time,
Hwa-chan is the winner.
You're not an ogre.
What are you scared of?
Here, just like this.
Oh, no.
For my neck!
I didn't listen to the rules, even for a second.
What?
Yes, Fa-chan wins.
I did it.
That was difficult.
My fingernail went up a little.My nails went up a little bit.
Let me try again.
Revenge.
Shall we?
I can't go on like this.
It's not going to end.
It's frustrating.
I'm sure there are lyrics like that.
Oh, I can't stop.
Go stand up.
We're filming, in case you were wondering.
Sorry.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
What do we do now?
Next, oni.
Let's decide who's going to be the demon.
I want to play!
Oh, no?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The second part, cucumber.
Cucumber sister.
Okay, let's play with the three of us except me.
First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors.
Oh!
I'm going to be an ogre, because I'm sure he's going to come up with a head.
That's not what I mean. I want to be an ogre.
I'll do it right.
Rock, paper, scissors.
It's aiko, right? It's aiko, right?
Yay!
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
Then, I'll do it.
Embroider the neck.Embroider the neck.
Please.
I'm scared.
This game is difficult.
It could be a disaster.
Kazugaru channel history.
What? Really?
For me.
I can't move.
Hmmm.
Even Toa-chan's expression was so controlled at first.
Hmm.
Okay, let's go.
I'll take Saki's picture too.
Yes, I will.
I see.
So it's like this, so quiet.
Well, well, well. It's the first time.
You're really repairing it.
Can't you see?
I can't make eye contact. You look like a mannequin.
Oh, no. I'm having a hard time.
Please dance your body as hard as you can.
It's your debut song.
Yes.
Oh, that sucks.
Yes, damn it.
Oh, the moves are annoying.
It's like an art painting.
Is it long?
Yeah, it's not long.
It's not long.
It's already out of place.
Yeah, it's fine.
It's okay, it's okay.
No, we're on the move.No, I'm on the move.
We're on the move?
This is the part where you tell me I can't do it.
They're not moving at all.
I'm gonna have to start messing with them.
I'm surprised they're not moving.
Why the hell not?
You still need to sleep.
I'm slipping.
It's okay.
That was close.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tighter, tighter, tighter.
Die.
Two, one, two, one,
Hey, why don't you guys move like that?
Yuzu's song choice?
Hey, hey.
I see. I see.
OK, OK!
Is that clear?
The first song is clear.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Are you waiting for the second song?
There's no such thing as clear.
No way.
So it's a leader system.
I usually do this when I'm stopped at the library.
I thought you were going to do it.
I knew you'd come.
That's right.
I knew it.
It's open.
Wow.
Please don't give me problems that I can't remember how to pretend.Please don't give me a problem that I can't remember how to pretend.
I made a mistake.
This move, I'm really going to stop now.
It's too hard.
Ah.
There's an action actress.
Okay?
I really want to stop. Stop right here.
I'm impressed.
Why are you all so eager to experience it?
It's Jim.
It's hot.
Thank you.
Right now.
What's wrong with this right now?
No, it's not good.
It's a little bigger...
It wasn't an eyeball.
Play it back. Play it back.
Absolutely not.
I can't do it.
No?
It's my fault that I just did that, right?
Yeah, you're right.
It's okay.
Wind.
It's hard.
...
Oh, yeah.
Come on ...
South Sanchaki is Sanchaki
I'm sure it's going to happen. It's already out ahead.
Oh, is this okay? This pose...
Left foot is strong. Left foot is strong.
They're not moving.
That's a strong one. You're out.This is strong. Out.
Life is so hard.
Let me introduce you to life. This is fun.
I'm tired. I'm tired. I'm tired.
So who's the winner?
Toa-chan wins on total points.
Congratulations!
Now, after all this...
I can't do it, my neck's shaking.
Then follow Lulu from the beginning.
Who's next? Who's next?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Otaru-chan!
So, thank you for watching.
Please subscribe and leave a comment.
Bye-bye.